# TRAN HUYNH NGOC MY

OFFICE ADMINISTRATOR

# **Objective**

Take advantages of skills and one-year experience in the field of Human Resources encompassing industries. Also, seeking to the position as Office Administrator in your respected organization as contribute my administrative abilities and interpersonal skills how I can significantly contribute to the on going of your reputable company.



# **Education -**

## HO CHI MINH CITY UNIVERSITY OF FOREIGN LANGUAGES AND INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (HUFLIT)

SEP 2020 - SEP 2016

Major: English as foreign language (EFL)

- DEGREE: Bachelor of Arts
- Speciality: Business English



# Work Experience -

#### KIDO FASHION COMPANY

**2017 - PRESENT** 

Warehouse and Sales Assistant

- Pick up, check and put goods in a warehouse every day.
- Manage and watch for the import-export goods in each branch.
- Manage goods in stock every week.
- Sell goods for Foreigners and Vietnamese at the Shop
- -Advertise products on media publications such as banners, posters, leaflets...
- -Recommend and display items that match customer needs.
- -Provide product, promotion, and pricing information by clarifying customer requests, selecting appropriate information.- Be assessed positively by the shop's boss: active, extremely adaptable...
- Observe, learn and catch customers' taste well.
- Improve English Communication Skill.

#### KIDO FASHION COMPANY

**2017 - PRESENT** 

Manager of Marketing and Customer Services Department

- Manage and take responsibility for all activities about the customer services
- Implement the process of receiving and processing customer requests
- Actively contact customers on holidays, gifts, or offers on special occasions
- Carry out information and advertising campaigns.
- Manage the company's marketing channel system: fanpage, website, email,...
- Report to superiors on the effectiveness of marketing activities
- Handle other arising situations.



- **H** June 6, 1997
- Female
- 093.3637.300
- mytranhuynh667@gmail.co
- P Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam
- i https://www.facebook.com/ mytranhuynh66

## **SKILLS** -

Time management skills

Communication skills

Teamwork/ Collaboration skills

Problem - solving

Written skills

**Public Speaking** 

## INTERESTS -

- Read book
- Music
- Travel



#### **DEPARTMENT OF FOREIGN LANGUAGE**

**JAN 2017 - FEB 2018** 

HUFLIT'S OPEN DAY

- Support team member.
- Work in a group with active members, and learn from each other.
- Making a plan, and giving ideal for programs.

## **PULSE ACTIVITIES**

2018 - 2019

HO CHI MINH CITY RUN

- Volunteer of HCMR 2018.
- Connect with the community.



# Certifications -

Test of English for International Communication (TOEIC) 600 score.

2019

Microsoft Office Specialist (MOS)

2019



# STRENGTHS/WEAKNESSES -

## **STRENGTHS**

- Analyze things carefully before starting any work.
- Self-motivated
- Punctuality My punctuality bounds me with the clock and provides me an opportunity to manage. My time intelligently and skillfully.
- Good listener and hard work.

## **WEAKNESSES**

- Spend a lot of time double-check.
- I always do my work with patience.
- Overthinking.